pioneer-audiovisual.eu 2016-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Pioneer

**PIONEERS COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

Your privacy is important to Pioneer & Onkyo Europe GmbH and its national sales subsidiaries and distributors in Europe and we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our privacy practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used.

**This privacy notice applies to following websites :**

pioneer-audiovisual.eu   
pioneer-audiovisual.de  
pioneer-audiovisual.at  
pioneer-audiovisual.ch  
pioneer-audiovisual.co.uk  
pioneer-audiovisual.fr  
pioneer-audiovisual.es  
pioneer-audiovisual.it  
pioneer-audiovisual.es  
pioneer-audiovisual.nl  
pioneer-audiovisual.be  
pioneer-audiovisual.gr  
pioneer-audiovisual.dk  
pioneer-audiovisual.fi  
pioneer-audiovisual.no  
pioneer-audiovisual.pt  
pioneer-audiovisual.ru  
pioneer-audiovisual.se  
pioneer-audiovisual.pl

Your use of these websites implies your agreement and acceptance of the clauses of our Privacy Policy. If this is not the case, then we request you not to provide us with any personal information.

**1\. What personal information do we collect?**

We request personal identifiable information when you register a product, request a service, answer a survey, enter a contest, correspond with us or engage in certain other activities on the above mentioned websites.

You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested personal information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction.

Similarly, when you visit our websites, we will collect information known as "clickstreams" (IP address, domain name, etc). This information, combined with the details you have provided us with, enables us to customize your visits better.

**2\. How do we use the information we collect?**

We use personal information in the following ways :  
1\. To provide you with information about product upgrades, new products, services, newsletters, informative emails and research on future product ideas or improvements;  
2\. To assist us in creating content that is relevant to you;  
3\. To provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you;  
4\. To assist us in creating better products and services to meet your needs;  
5\. To allow you to download documents, obtain access to services or otherwise engage in activities you select; and  
6\. To help you quickly find software, services or product information important to you.

**3\. How do we protect your personal information ?**

In order to guarantee the security of your personal information we have set in place a series of security measures and safeguards. Your personal information is stored on secure networks that may only be accessed by a limited number of persons holding special access rights and who undertake to respect and maintain its confidential nature.

Despite these measures, whenever you provide personal information on the Internet, there is always a risk that it may be intercepted and used by third persons whom we are unable to control. Although we make every effort to protect your personal information and privacy, we are unable to guarantee the security of the information you make available over the internet.

**4\. Who has access to your personal information and to what extent?**

In addition to the companies mentioned and for the purposes described above, we do not sell, trade or transfer your personal information in any form to third parties without informing you first and in accordance with the personal information protection legislation currently in effect.

Your personal information may be transferred to outside contractors to provide services for us. They may be used to provide technical support. We require that these contractors keep your personal information secure and confidential. We also require that these contractors use personal information only on behalf of Pioneer & Onkyo Europe GmbH.

At all time you may opt out for the sharing of your personal information with third parties. This can be done via the account page of our online registration area.

When you submit a product review, your nickname and country can be openly viewed by others. Depending on your Shared settings, which can be changed at any time via the account page of our online registration area, you also share your first name, photo, and links.

**5\. Links**

In order to improve the services offered by our websites, we may include links to websites of third parties. PIONEER is not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours. PIONEER cannot be liable, nor may it be considered as such, for the contents and activities of these websites.

**6\. Cookies**

PIONEER websites may use the industry-wide technology called cookies. A cookie is a unique text file that a website sends to your browser software. Cookies enable a website to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. PIONEER may use cookies to personalize your pages, or to remember you when you register products or services. If you do not want PIONEER to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some of the services at our PIONEER websites.  
PIONEER also uses cookies to track the visits to our websites. The Information hereby gathered helps us to optimize the websites' content, navigation and performance.

**7\. Choices and opt-out**

PIONEER provides a number of ways for you to review, edit or delete your personal information or to 'opt out' of receiving additional information from us. We may offer you these choices at the same time you give us personal information.

You may also review, update or delete your account by editing your Account and profile settings in the registration area. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

If you experience difficulties in changing or deleting your personal information you may contact us (details below) for assistance.

**8\. Changes to the privacy policy**

Over time, we may opt to modify or update this policy either due to changes in legislation or in order to cover new internet developments. We therefore reserve the right to carry out any such changes and request that you visit this page regularly, as these changes may affect you as a visitor to our website.

**9\. Contact us**

Should you have questions about this privacy policy, the privacy aspects of our products and services or would like to make a complaint, please contact :

Pioneer & Onkyo Europe GmbH  
Zweigniederlassung Willich  
Hanns-Martin-Schleyer-Straße 35  
D-47877 Willich  
GERMANY

Fon: +49 (0) 2154 - 913-130  
Fax: +49 (0) 02154 - 429-670

**10\. Who administers the personal information?**

Both our websites and the information collected are administered and controlled by Pioneer & Onkyo Europe GmbH. Our website servers and hosts are located in Germany. Pioneer & Onkyo Europe GmbH has signed agreements with the companies that host its websites in order to offer sufficient guarantees regarding the protection of your personal information. Personal information is administered in accordance with current legislation regarding the protection of personal information as well as this privacy policy. To ensure that your personal information is protected, Pioneer & Onkyo Europe GmbH has certified its privacy policy with the German Privacy Commission, a commission overseeing whether the processing and use of personal information is compliant with the German Data Protection Act.
